<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Battery Destroyer</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">System Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_system">Test Steps</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About Swipe</string>
    <string name="menu_legal">Legal Matters</string>
    <string name="logo_text">
        2013 Swipe Development.Inc. All rights reserved Swipe Development....
    </string>
    <string name="power_default_value">1</string>
    <string name="video_default_id">1</string>

	<string name="about_swipe"> Welcome to Swipe Development Inc. Swipe Development Inc. and/or its affiliates provide mobile development consulting, specializing in mobile battery drain analysis. Swipe Development provides our services subject to the following conditions. 

By using the Battery Destroyer application, you agree to these conditions. Please read them carefully.</string>
	<string name="about_copyright">
COPYRIGHT All content included in or made available through any Swipe Development application, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, and data compilations is the property of Swipe Development or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content included in or made available through any Swipe Development employee is the exclusive property of Swipe Development and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.</string>
	<string name="about_trademarks">TRADEMARKS
In addition, graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts, and service names included in or made available through Swipe Development are trademarks or trade dress of Swipe Development in the U.S. and other countries. Swipe Development’s trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not Swipe Development’s, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits Swipe Development. 
	    
	</string>
	<string name="swipe_address1">Swipe Development Inc.</string>
	<string name="swipe_address2">330 A Street, Suite 188</string>
	<string name="swipe_address3">San Diego, CA 92101 </string>
	<string name="about_copyright_title">Copyright © 2013 Swipe Development \n All Rights Reserved </string>
	<string name="homepage">http://swipedevelopment.com</string>
</resources>